let MCQS = [{
    question: "how long will it take the Earth to make complete a rotation ?",
    choice1: "365 days",
    choice2: "60 Minutes",
    choice3: "3600 seconds",
    choice4: "24 hours",
    answer: 3
},
            {
            question: "Ade's last birthday was Febuary 29, 2020. is next birthday will be?",
    choice1: "Febuary 29, 2024",
    choice2: "Febuary 29, 2023",
    choice3: "Febuary 29, 2022",
    choice4: "Febuary 29, 2021",
    answer: 0
},
            {
            question: "The probability that Buhari will loss 2023 election is 1 because?",
    choice1: "Buhari didn't have a politcal party",
    choice2: "Buhari is not the people's choice",
    choice3: "Buhari is not a presidential candidate",
    choice4: "Buhari failed Nigeria for two terms",
    answer: 2
},
            {
            question: "That John is an aspirant of FUNAAB makes him a/an?",
    choice1: "Undergraduate",
    choice2: "Student",
    choice3: "Postgraduate",
    choice4: "Jambite",
    answer: 1
},
            {
            question: "Shalewa is a Nigerian and he has a Voters Card, it means she's?",
    choice1: "18 years old",
    choice2: "More than 18 years old",
    choice3: "Eligible to vote",
    choice4: "a candidate",
    answer: 2
},
            {
            question: "Chinedu scored 40 in an examination, if the pass mark is 39 it means?",
    choice1: "Have a carryover",
    choice2: "Failed the examination",
    choice3: "Didn't prepare for the examination",
    choice4: "Passed the examination",
    answer: 3
},
            {
               question: "which of these is not an academic body?",
    choice1: "ASUU",
    choice2: "NASU",
    choice3: "ASUP",
    choice4: "NAT",
    answer: 1
},{
               question: "If Dayo is a colphysite, it means he is?",
    choice1: "a funaabite",
    choice2: "in chemistry department",
    choice3: "an outstanding student",
    choice4: "competitive",
    answer: 0
},
            {
               question: "Which of these is not a TV reality show?",
    choice1: "Ultimate Search",
    choice2: "BIg Brother Naija",
    choice3: "Nigeria Idol",
    choice4: "Funsab Make we yarn",
    answer: 3
},
            {
               question: "Which of these is in the right order of authority?",
    choice1: "SUG President",
    choice2: "Vice Chancellor",
    choice3: "Welfare Director",
    choice4: "Head of Class",
    answer: 3
}];